### **ANNA FEDOTOVA**

### Senior Data Analyst

### **PROFILE**

Digital business enthusiast with 5+ years of experience translating data into products and business strategies. Skilled communicator able to explain complex concepts in an easy-to-understand way. Lifelong learning advocate passionate about sharing knowledge and mentorship.



linkedin com/in/annafedotova



annafedotova.github.io/workshops-portfolio/

### **SKILLS**

- · Programming stack: Python, SQL, Git
- Analytics stack: Tableau, Looker, Amplitude, Segment, Google Analytics, Google Tag Manager
- Languages: English (fluent), Spanish (fluent), Russian (native)

### **AREAS OF EXPERTISE**

- Product Analytics
- Product Experimentation
- Growth Funnels
- User Research
- Data Infrastructure
- Data Visualization
- Instructional Design

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- 4YFN Datathon finalist, 2019
- Headway Digital employee of the year, 2017
- GMAT: 760 / 800, 99 percentile

### **CONTACT INFORMATION**

Mobile +(34) 644 053 987

Email admi.fedotova@gmail.com

Location EU timezone

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## SuperDataScience, Online Learning Platform Remote, 2020 - now Data Analyst (Oct 2020 - Present)

- Designing experiments, defining success metrics, and assessing the expected and actual impact of product & growth initiatives (A/B testing)
- Establishing scalable and centralized data infrastructure from scratch (BigQuery, Stitch ETLs, Segment event tracking, Tableau)
- Fostering data-driven company culture by providing training, sharing exploratory analysis insights, and enabling decision-makers to access the necessary data

#### Data Instructor and Mentor (Oct 2020 - Present)

- Designing new learning programs (Data Scientist Learning Path) as a combination of courses, practical projects, and career assignments
- Creating practical workshops for students to enrich their data project portfolio (SQL, A/B testing, Tableau, Applied Business Analytics)
- Holding 1-to-1 coaching sessions to help learners navigate the field of data science and build a personalized learning plan
- Providing technical support and solving student community inquiries related to the content of the courses and projects

# Allwomen Academy, Tech Bootcamp Barcelona, 2019 - 2020 Data Visualization Instructor (Apr 2019 - Dec 2020)

• Gave an introduction to data visualization with a practical 3-hour workshop to all students in Data Science and Data Analytics tracks

# TravelPerk, Business Travel Platform Barcelona, 2019 - 2020 Data Analyst (Jul 2019 - Sep 2020)

- Led multiple analytical projects within product and growth teams (definition of activation, multi-touch attribution, Product Qualified Lead)
- Designed and implemented actionable metrics, dashboards, and reports (Looker)
- Developed quantitative analysis to drive product and business decisions

### **PUBLIC SPEAKING & TEACHING**

#### A/B Test Results Analysis in Tableau, DSGO Virtual

Apr 2021

 Designed and delivered a practical workshop to an online audience of 80 people

#### Jury Panel Member at Data Analytics Bootcamp, Ironhack Mar 2020

 Assessed and gave constructive feedback to the bootcamp graduates on their final project presentations

### Build your first dashboard in Dash, PyDay BCN

Nov 2019

2018

 Designed and delivered a practical workshop to an offline audience of 60 Python enthusiasts

### **EDUCATION**

## Activation and Retention Strategy Udacity 2021

## Data Product Manager Nanodegree 2020 Udacity

Focus on product experimentation and data infrastructure

### Data Analyst Nanodegree

Udacity

Bertelsmann Scholarship Recipient

### Master in International Management 2013 - 2014

ESADE Business School

Average grade - 8,8 out of 10